mrscleanusa.com 2013-11-29

# Privacy Policy | Mrs Clean House Cleaning & Maid Service

Your privacy is protected with us. We will not sell, rent, release, or otherwise disseminate your personal information without your permission.

You may visit [Mrs. Clean](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/ "Mrs. Clean housecleaning and maid service") without revealing any personal information about yourself.

[Mrs. Clean](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/mrs-clean/about-us.html "About Mrs. clean") uses statistical tracking software to provide metrics of site visitors and page views. The software may use cookies to track user navigation of the site for summary reporting only.

## Contact Information

## Phone:

Redmond: (425) 285-4494 & (425) 881-8411  
Lynnwood: (425) 787-9252   
Mill Creek: (425) 357-3432  
Seattle: (888) 253-2607  
Toll Free: (888) Clean-07

## Fax:

Main: (425) 787-9283  
Administration: (425) 337-7286

## Corporate Mailing Address:

P.O. Box 12001  
Mill Creek, WA. 98082

## Redmond Office:

8201 164th Ave NE, Suite 200,

Redmond, WA, 98052

Voice: +1 (425) 285-4494

Voice: +1 (425) 881-8411

Toll Free: +1 (888) 253-2607

Fax: +1 (425) 629-6202

## Lynnwood Office:

3223 164th ST SW #M  
Lynnwood, WA. 98087-3214

Voice: +1 (425) 787-9252

Fax: +1 (425) 787-9283

Toll Free: +1 (888) 253-2607

## Contact Mrs. Clean House Cleaning and Maid Service:

Email: [info@mrscleanusa.com](mailto:info@mrscleanusa.com)   

[Mrs. Clean's House Cleaning and Maid Service](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/), [Cleaning Blog](http://mrscleanusa.blogspot.com/), [Cleaning Tips on Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/cleaningtips), [Mrs Clean on Twitter](https://twitter.com/mrscleanusa), [Mrs Clean on Linkedin](http://www.linkedin.com/in/corinaw).

## Dispute Resolution

Disputes will be handled by our customer service representative. Our customer service department will promptly correct any errors.

## Data Collection

Personal information (name, address, email, phone, home specs) is required if you request an [online house cleaning estimate](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/maid-service/house-cleaning-estimate.html "Free cleaning estimate"). Other than using this information to verify your service area and review your home specs to provide an accurate cleaning estimate, this data is discarded and not used by us further in any way.

Persons who supply their phone number on-line to request a cleaning quote will only receive telephone or email contact from us regarding clarification for house cleaning or scheduling of services they have placed on-line.

Personal information is required to post information (name, email) in the house cleaning forum.

Mrs. Clean uses statistical tracking software for analysis of site volume. This software may use cookies to track user navigation for summary reporting only. We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as automatic forum logon.

We collect, (but do not use further) the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address).

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our web site.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site , ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

## Ad Servers

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with selected companies that we allow to place ads on our web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

  * [Amazon privacy policy](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496).
  * [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

## Security

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site, We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mail, calling or mailing us at the above addresses.

Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number, The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at [mgoldberger@the-dma.org](mailto:mgoldberger@the-dma.org), state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office.

[House Cleaning FAQ](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/maid-service/frequently-asked-questions.html) House Cleaning & Maid Service FAQ These are the most frequently asked questions about getting started with Mrs Clean's House Cleaning and Maid Service. If you've had all your questions answered, you can&n... [ More detail](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/maid-service/frequently-asked-questions.html)

[Cleaning Estimate](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/maid-service/house-cleaning-estimate.html) Request a House Cleaning/Maid Service/Office Cleaning Estimate You work hard. You deserve a clean home. Mrs. Clean is ready and waiting to serve you. Are you ready for a cleaning company that's dependable, affordable... [ More detail](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/maid-service/house-cleaning-estimate.html)

[Client Testimonials](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/mrs-clean/testimonials.html) Company Testimonials We are proud of delighting our clients and receiving feedback on their quality house cleaning. Mrs. Clean is committed to your clean home with our 100% guaranteed maid services. Our Servi... [ More detail](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/mrs-clean/testimonials.html)

[Customer Promise](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/mrs-clean/what-to-expect.html) What to Expect From Mrs. Clean House Cleaning and Maid Service Mrs. Clean's promise to our valued clients. A Guaranteed House Cleaning If you are not completely satisfied with your house cleaning, contact us... [ More detail](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/mrs-clean/what-to-expect.html)

[Company Mission](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/mrs-clean/our-mission.html) Mrs. Clean's House Cleaning Mission Statement Mrs. Clean's mission is to enrich the lives of our clients through superior quality house cleaning, legendary customer service, and the highest level of customer s... [ More detail](http://www.mrscleanusa.com/en/cleaning-services/mrs-clean/our-mission.html)
